"Vox didn't have an answer for that and didn't try to build one.

"I don't like handing you a maybe."

"I don't need a maybe to be a yes," Rook said.

"I need it to be a number I have and PEREGRINE doesn't know I have." She looked at the name once more before Vox closed the channel on it — a string of letters attached to a person she would never meet, and a man who'd reached into his own log by hand to make sure no trace of the looking survived him. That was the part worth keeping. Not the name. The care he'd taken with it.

"Watch for it again. If he goes looking a second time, I want to know before PEREGRINE does."

(1 rows affected)
